export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: Artificial Intelligence";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "What is intelligence primarily defined as in the text?",
        optionA: "The ability to act in a situation",
        optionB:
          "The ability to understand and learn from previous experiences",
        optionC: "The ability to observe living beings",
        correctAnswer:
          "The ability to understand and learn from previous experiences",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is an example of Natural Intelligence?",
        optionA: "A smartphone performing various tasks",
        optionB: "Sunflowers changing direction to face the sun",
        optionC: "A smart television providing entertainment",
        correctAnswer: "Sunflowers changing direction to face the sun",
      },
      {
        question:
          "In the context of Natural Intelligence, where is this ability observed?",
        optionA: "Only in humans",
        optionB: "Only in animals",
        optionC: "In living beings like plants, animals, and humans",
        correctAnswer: "In living beings like plants, animals, and humans",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What does Artificial Intelligence primarily refer to in the text?",
        optionA: "Ability to act autonomously",
        optionB: "Ability of digital computers to perform tasks",
        optionC: "Ability to observe and learn from surroundings",
        correctAnswer: "Ability of digital computers to perform tasks",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which device utilizes Artificial Intelligence to connect people globally?",
        optionA: "Smartphones",
        optionB: "Smart Television",
        optionC: "Digital Gadgets",
        correctAnswer: "Smartphones",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What action exemplifies Natural Intelligence in humans according to the text?",
        optionA: "Watching television",
        optionB: "Closing eyes in bright light",
        optionC: "Using a smartphone",
        correctAnswer: "Closing eyes in bright light",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Where is Artificial Intelligence observed, as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Only in smartphones",
        optionB: "Only in digital gadgets",
        optionC: "In digital gadgets like smartphones, television, etc.",
        correctAnswer: "In digital gadgets like smartphones, television, etc.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which natural entity changes its direction to face the sun, as mentioned in the text?",
        optionA: "Humans",
        optionB: "Animals",
        optionC: "Sunflowers",
        correctAnswer: "Sunflowers",
      },
      {
        question:
          "What aspect of a smart television involves Artificial Intelligence?",
        optionA: "Its ability to display colors vividly",
        optionB: "Entertaining through various means like music, movies, etc.",
        optionC: "Connecting to the internet wirelessly",
        correctAnswer:
          "Entertaining through various means like music, movies, etc.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "According to the text, what characteristic defines Natural Intelligence?",
        optionA: "Acting autonomously based on past experiences",
        optionB: "Mimicking human behavior",
        optionC: "Adapting to new situations instantly",
        correctAnswer: "Acting autonomously based on past experiences",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "___________ is the ability to think, understand, and learn from previous experiences to act in a situation.",
        optionA: "Intelligence",
        optionB: "Knowledge",
        optionC: "Wisdom",
        correctAnswer: "Intelligence",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Natural Intelligence is observed in living beings like plants, animals, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Inanimate objects",
        optionB: "Microorganisms",
        optionC: "Humans",
        correctAnswer: "Humans",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Our eyes automatically get closed when bright light hits our face, showcasing an example of Natural Intelligence in ___________.",
        optionA: "Animals",
        optionB: "Plants",
        optionC: "Humans",
        correctAnswer: "Humans",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence is the ability of digital computers or computer-controlled gadgets to perform tasks commonly done by ___________.",
        optionA: "Humans",
        optionB: "Machines",
        optionC: "Animals",
        correctAnswer: "Humans",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Smartphones use artificial intelligence to perform various tasks, including connecting people ___________.",
        optionA: "Locally",
        optionB: "Globally",
        optionC: "Nationally",
        correctAnswer: "Globally",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Sunflowers change direction to face the sun during the daytime, demonstrating Natural Intelligence in ___________.",
        optionA: "Animals",
        optionB: "Plants",
        optionC: "Humans",
        correctAnswer: "Plants",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence is observed in digital gadgets like smartphones, television, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Computers",
        optionB: "Cameras",
        optionC: "Watches",
        correctAnswer: "Television",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Smart televisions use artificial intelligence to entertain people through various means like music, movies, and ___________.",
        optionA: "Educational programs",
        optionB: "Documentaries",
        optionC: "Using the internet",
        correctAnswer: "Using the internet",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Natural Intelligence is characterized by acting autonomously based on past experiences, without ___________.",
        optionA: "Learning",
        optionB: "Mimicking",
        optionC: "External programming",
        correctAnswer: "External programming",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence refers to the ability of digital computers to perform tasks which are commonly done by ___________.",
        optionA: "Animals",
        optionB: "Machines",
        optionC: "Plants",
        correctAnswer: "Animals",
      },
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Natural Intelligence is observed only in humans.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question: "Artificial Intelligence is solely limited to smartphones.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Smartphones utilize Natural Intelligence for various functions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence is characterized by the ability of computers to perform tasks done by humans.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Plants can exhibit Natural Intelligence based on their responses to environmental stimuli.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence is exclusively found in digital gadgets like televisions.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Natural Intelligence relies heavily on external programming for decision-making.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Artificial Intelligence enables smartphones to connect people globally.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Sunflowers changing direction to face the sun demonstrates Natural Intelligence.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "True",
      },
      {
        question:
          "Smart televisions use Artificial Intelligence solely for displaying colors vividly.",
        optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",correctAnswer: "False",
      },
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
